Full name:

Mikhail Katsman

Phone number:Email address:Location:+(44) 7462 855 705mkatdev@outlook.comLondon, UK

Dev portfolio link:Interior design link:www.mkat.devwww.cubikadesign.com

Info

As a former director of an interior design bureau for 9 years, I have developed a strong skill set in project management, where I successfully led a team of 8 people to complete multiple projects on time and within budget. I was responsible for overseeing the entire project lifecycle, from client consultation to final delivery, and I had to ensure that all team members were working together effectively and efficiently.

This experience allowed me to develop strong communication, problem-solving, and time-management skills, which I believe would translate well to a career in web development. I am confident that I can use these skills to contribute to the success of any project or team that I am a part of, and I am excited to continue growing my skills in the IT industry.

skills

Web Development:Mobile Development:Design tools:HTML, Javascript, CSS,Dart,Photoshop, Illustrator,React.js, Next.js,Flutter,InDesign, 3DsMax,Node.js, MongoDBFirebaseAutoCAD

Experience

Graphic Designer at **Baltic Restaurants Ltd.** / Kaliningrad, Russia / Aug 2009 - Sep 2010 As a self-taught graphic designer helped develop multiple restaurant/bar menus, promotional material and company's visit cards. Largest contribution being develoment of branding material and packaging design for a large product line of frozen foods under the brand "Proba".

Director / Interior Designer at **Cubika Design Ltd.** / London, UK / Jul 2013 - Aug 2022 Created an interior design bureau with my business partner. Specialised in both residential and commercial spaces. Successfuly completed multiple small and large (1000m.sq+) projects in UK, Russia and France.

NOWS App / Flutter mobile application

NOWS app is essentially a social network of user created pins (or posts) consisting of geolocation metadata, title and description text and image or video data. Pins are displayed on an interactive map within a certain radius of each user.



Education

TK Portfolio / Static website

This static website uses basic web-development tools and a custom node.js page generator to produce a photography portfolio with gallery view for each portfolio entry.

Website is fully responsive to mobile/desktop. Mobile pinch/swipe actions are implemented.

MK Portfolio / Next.js website

I have experemented with an isometric general layout for my portfolio website, utilizing a component based development approach, CSS and custom modules, Next.js SSR, static page generation and multiple React 'hook' features.

BA Interior Design

Istituto Marangoni London / Sep 2010 - Jun 2013

CS50x Computer Science

Harvard Online Education / Jul 2022 - Sep 2022

Online courses:

The Complete **Dart** Learning Guide [2022 Edition] / Oct 2022

Flutter 3 with Flutter Projects on Dart Programming Language / Oct 2022

Build Responsive Real-World Websites with **HTML** and **CSS** / Jan 2023

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux, Next.js, GIT) / Feb 2023

